adasiaholdings.com 2019-01-05

# AnyMind Group | Privacy Policy

## Privacy policy for AnyMind Group websites

AnyMind Group has adopted these privacy principles for the organization’s online properties, including anymindgroup.com, adasiaholdings.com, casting-asia.com, talentmind.ai and moments-asia.com.

AnyMind Group and its subsidiaries are firmly committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users and fostering user confidence in the Internet, Internet advertising and direct marketing. Accordingly, we are committed to observing applicable industry guidelines including those established jointly by the Interactive Advertising Bureau. We continually evaluate innovative ways to protect online user privacy while also seeking to deliver relevant advertising and custom online experiences on behalf of our clients.

This notice also explains your rights as someone who may provide personal data to AnyMind Group through the Websites and how to exercise these rights. If you are an individual residing in the European Economic Area (EEA) or Switzerland you should be aware that our DPO can contacted at dpo@anymindgroup.com.

The purpose of this privacy policy is to provide clear notice about the user information we may collect online in connection with AnyMind Group’s online properties (including forementioned websites).

The next few sections below describe how we collect user information in connection with the operation of our online properties, such as through advertisements that may appear on various websites on the Internet. Therefore, certain information collection by AnyMind Group through the use of cookies, as described below, may occur on numerous websites across the Internet. 

For information on how we collect and use information that is collected directly on this website, please see the section entitled "Information We Collect".

We use some or all of this information to improve your website experience by delivering content that you are likely to prefer on future visits. Our lawful basis for this type of processing is that we have a legitimate interest in understanding and improving your experience of our Website.  
If you don’t agree to us using cookies and the above information, you may prevent their use through your browser settings or you may choose to opt out at https://www.youradchoices.com/. By choosing not to accept cookies, certain Website features may not work as we have intended.

## Information We Collect

We do not collect personally identifiable information ("PII") from users online through advertisements unless users affirmatively and deliberately choose to release that information by submitting it, in a text field for example. PII generally refers to identifying information such as an individual's name, mailing address, phone number or e-mail address. 

## Non-Personal Information Collected

We do collect non-personally identifiable information ("Non-PII) to identify computers that we have interacted with before. For instance, by using Non-PII, we may be able to identify a computer that has previously seen an advertisement by us. In the context of Non-PII, whenever we refer to ‘you' or ‘yours,' please remember that we may be referring to a computer and not an identifiable person since we generally do not know who is using a computer at any particular time.

Through the collection and use of Non-PII, we have a range of services to show you the most useful and relevant online advertisements across numerous websites and to prevent excessive or repeated deliveries of the same advertisements. For example, if a user is interested in advertising solutions, then we may deliver interest-based online advertisements to you about a particular type of advertising solution. You can learn more about such advertising practices by visiting www.iab.net/privacymatters.

We may collect Non-PII regarding your web browsing, usage or interactions with advertisements. We do this to better customize the sort of advertisements you see on various websites and for other purposes such as research and analysis. Non-PII may include information such as the type of Internet browser used by an online user, the type of computer operating system used, the computer's Internet protocol ("IP") address, the domain name of the websites visited before and after viewing an advertisement, as well as information related to websites and web pages a user is viewing when an advertisement is shown. 

We collect Non-PII through the use of cookies, pixels and related technologies. A cookie is a file on your browser that uniquely identifies your browser and computer. A pixel is a line of code which is used by a website or third party to assign online activities to a computer or browser. The use of a pixel allows websites and us to record, for example, that a user has visited a particular web page. Additional Non-PII from an earlier period or interaction may be included in the pixel. Though Non-PII does not personally identify anyone, we are still committed to giving users the opportunity to exercise choice about the Non-PII we collect. 

## Specific cookie types used

### Performance Analytics tracking

This type of cookie provides aggregated information about where a user may go on the Website.

### Google Analytics (persistent)

AnyMind Group uses Google Analytics to help analyze how visitors use the Website. Among other things, Google Analytics uses cookies to collect information about the number of visits to the Website, the webpage that referred visitors to the Website, language, device, browser and operating system, the pages visitors view within the Website and other similar details. We do not share this information with third parties. When used this way the Google Analytics cookie is a persistent cookie, and will remain on your device until the cookie expires or you delete it. These cookies may appear as _utm, _utma, _utmb, _utmc, _utmz, _utmv, _utmt, _gid.

### Google Analytics (session)

This cookie may appear as has_js. We do not retain this data as it is deleted upon closing of your browser, and therefore we cannot share it with any third parties.

### Social Media

These are cookies that help with the website’s functionality. These are third party cookies and they allow you to share comments, pages, bookmarks and likes and help to provide access to social networking tools easily.

### Socal Sharing

Social media widgets used on this Website include LinkedIn, Twitter and YouTube. These social media widgets collect information about your visit to the Website and your use of the social platform services (for example, buttons or likes) on the Website. We do not share information with these social platforms, however please keep in mind the social networks collect the data of your site visit and interaction with the social widget directly.

### Third-Party Services

We may use cookies and pixels from third party providers – such as Google, Facebook and others – on our website to help provide more relevant experiences for you as a user. Such cookie or pixel may be implemented on a AnyMind Group company website which tags a visitor of the site, so that the visitor may be identified and advertisements can be served on that visitor via the relevant platforms.

If you wish to opt-out of any of these please do so by either using the privacy controls offered by these specific platforms or by using a recognised opt-out service such as: https://www.youradchoices.com/

## Data Subject Rights of Individuals in the EEA and Switzerland

You have the right to access, update, change, delete, restrict the use of, or obtain a copy of your Personal Data in an easily readable format. In certain circumstances, you may also request that AnyMind Group transfer your Personal Data to a third party, and the right to object to its use for marketing purposes. If you wish to exercise any of these rights please contact our DPO at dpo@anymindgroup.com. Where our processing of your personal data is based on your consent, you also have the right to withdraw this consent at any time by contacting our DPO at dpo@anymindgroup.com. Please note that your withdrawal of consent will not affect the lawfulness of our processing of your personal data prior to withdrawal of consent.

## Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

We do not collect PII via our client's advertisements, and therefore, we do not sell, rent, or share PII collected on our or other websites to non-affiliated third parties. If you affirmatively and deliberately provide PII via one of our client's advertisements who was identified to you at the time of collection, then that PII will be provided to such client, and such PII shall be subject to that client's privacy policy.

We may disclose a user's Non-PII to third parties when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including, but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person. In addition and if permitted by applicable law, we may also disclose and provide access to a user's PII and Non-PII to our vendors and contractors who are performing services on our behalf. However, such vendors and contractors are not permitted to use such user information for any purpose other than providing services to us.

## User Choice - Opting Out of Receiving Cookies

We use technology, which includes cookies, in the delivery of our marketing activities. We believe that the use of these tools enables us to provide users with a more meaningful web experience.

At all times, you may adjust your computer's web browser settings to refuse all cookies. However, by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the websites you visit or take full advantage of all the website offerings and interest-based advertising. You can remove cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file.

## Data Retention

We may use our anonymous cookie information for advertising purposes for up to 14 months. 

## Information Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect against the unauthorized access to, retention of, and disclosure of information. This includes undertaking necessary physical, electronic, and management activities required to protect information integrity, access, and use. Any information that is stored on our server is treated as confidential information. Please keep in mind, however, that despite these reasonable efforts to protect information on our servers, no method of transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your information at all times, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Change to this Privacy Policy

Please note that because of the changing nature of privacy laws, user needs, and our business, we may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time by providing advance notice on our website before implementing such modifications. Accordingly, since we want to help you clearly understand our Privacy Policy, and any pertinent revisions, we encourage you to review our Privacy Policy periodically to become aware of any changes that may have occurred.

## Information We Collect Through Your Correspondence on this Website

If you provide us information through our "contact us" link on anymindgroup.com, adasiaholdings.com, casting-asia.com, talentmind.ai and moments-asia.com, sign up to receive our marketing emails or newsletters, submit information in connection with an employment inquiry, expressly enter information into a text field or otherwise submit information to us, we will keep a record of the information you provide including your email address and any other PII you provide solely for the purpose of responding to your inquiry or to provide you with requested marketing materials or newsletters. Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, this information will never be shared with third parties without your consent. AnyMind Group may pass your PII to our subsidiaries and affiliated companies so that they may contact you in connection with the objective of your inquiry. Where we pass your PII to our subsidiary or affiliated companies in another country, we will make sure that they apply the same level of protection to your information as we do. We may also disclose your information to third parties in the event of suspected fraud, legal requirement or in connection with our vendors and contractors, all as described above.

AnyMind Group may use cookies to tailor your experience on our website (this website) and to help provide a better service to you. You may opt out of cookies used on our websites through the instructions provided above.

If you would like us to remove your information from our marketing e-mails or newsletters, please contact us at privacy@adasiaholdings.com. Be sure to include your name, username and clear instructions regarding any change to your PII including email address or if you would like us to unsubscribe you from our database. 

## Children's Privacy

We are sensitive to the issue of children's privacy. Therefore, our websites are neither developed for, nor directed at, children. If you believe your child has provided us with PII, and you would like to have the information removed, please contact us at privacy@adasiaholdings.com.

## Linking to Other Websites

A link from our own website to another website does not imply our endorsement of that website. We do not control the websites to which we link and assume no responsibility for their content or privacy policies. Therefore, you should carefully review the privacy policies that apply to any websites you access from our website.

## Transfer of Data upon Change of Control

In the event that another company acquires all or substantially all of the assets of our business through a consolidation, merger, asset purchase, or other transaction, we reserve the right to transfer all information (including any PII a user may have provided through the "contact us" page) that is in our possession or under our control to such acquiring party.

## Questions or Comments about this Privacy Policy

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact us through email or by mail. You can address your general questions and comments by e-mail to privacy@adasiaholdings.com or dpo@anymindgroup.com, or by mail: #13-01 SBF Center, 160 Robinson Road, Singapore 068914 Attn: Data Protection Officer

Updated: 25 May 2018
